Contact

+380957508021 (Mobile) mikedatsik@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mykhailodatsyk (LinkedIn) mikedatsik.com (Personal) postmodern.digital (Company) vimeo.com/user5084610 (Portfolio)

Top Skills

VFX Supervision

Pipeline

Houdini

Languages

Ukrainian (Native or Bilingual)

Russian (Native or Bilingual)

English (Professional Working)

Honors-Awards

VES Awards 2014

VES Awards 2013

FICCI BAF 2014

Mykhailo Datsyk

Chief Technical Officer at POSTMODERN Digital Ukraine

Summary

Filmography:

2018: 2.0

2017: The Stronghold 2015-2016: Forsaken

2014 : War Thunder "Victory is ours" - cinematic trailer

2014 : Speak of the devil

2014: Viy 3D

2013 : Inseparable

2012 : Match

2012 : Vasiliy Stalin 2012 : Polar Race

2012: Chapays passions

2011: The Bomber

2009 : Target

IMDB credits:

https://www.imdb.com/name/nm6218686/?ref_=nv_sr_1

I'am a Technical Director specialising in FX using Houdini, Pipeline TD, Computer graphics Research with over 10 years of experience working on feature films and commercials. Currently CTO at three times VES nominated company "Postmodern Digital" in Kiev, Ukraine.

Specialties:

Team management for more than 40 people.

Projects and On-set Supervising.

Technical:

Houdini TD, Maya, Nuke, Programming (Python, c++), Studio Pipeline Workflow Design.

Research in field of image rendering and computer graphics data store.

Experience

POSTMODERN CTO of Postmodern Digital February 2017 - Present Kiev Region, Ukraine

http://postmodern.digital

POSTMODERN VFX Supervisor, TD February 2011 - January 2016 (5 years) Kiev, Ukraine

Gvardiya Film Production House CG Artist November 2008 - January 2011 (2 years 3 months) Kiev Region, Ukraine

Education

Kharkiv National University of Radioelectronics Magister, Computer Science, Information Control System Department · (2003 - 2008)